Gross, Robert; Papers apap291
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, Subject Files, 1973-1995; 2; 5.2 cubic ft.
  - National- National Interreligious Task Force on Criminal Justice, 1990; 1992-1995; Undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - National- National Interreligious Task Force on Criminal Justice, Undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - National- National Lawyers Guild, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - National- National Legal Aid and Defender Association, 1989; 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - National- National Organizers Alliance, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - National- National Prison Project, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - National- National Urban League, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - National- Nova, Undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - National- Partition Defense Committee, 1989-1990; 1992-1994; Undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - National- Pox Christi, 1987-1989; Undated (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - National- Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program, 1977; 1987-1995; Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - National- Prisoner Visitation and Support, 1988; 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - National- Rocky Mountain Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1986; 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - National- Sentencing Project, 1987-1994; Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - National- Southern Christian Leadership Conference, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - National- Southern Coalition on Jails and Prisons, 1981-1991; Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - National- Southern Prisoners' Defense Committee, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - National- Union of American Hebrew Congregations, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - National- Unitarian Universalist Service Committee, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - National- United Methodist Church, 1989; 1993 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - National- War Resisters League, 1990-1991; 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Nebraska- Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1981-1991; Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Nebraska Correspondence, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Nebraska Miscellaneous, 1988; 1990-1993; Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Nebraska- Other Organizations, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Nevada- Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1986; Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Nevada Correspondence, 1987; 1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Nevada- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Nevada Miscellaneous, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Nevada- Other Organizations, 1988-1990; Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - New Hampshire- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - New Hampshire Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - New Jersey- Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1984-1985; 1987; 1990-1991; Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - New Jersey Correspondence, 1984; 1986; Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - New Jersey- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - New Jersey Miscellaneous, 1984-1986; 1991-1992; Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - New Jersey- Other Organizations, 1985-1986; 1989-1990; Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - New Jersey- PALM, 1988-1989; 1991; Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - New Mexico- Committee to Stop Executions, 1982-1985; 1991-1992; 1994; Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - New Mexico Correspondence, 1981-1992; Undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - New Mexico- Lifelines, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - New Mexico Miscellaneous, 1982-1984; 1987; Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - New Mexico- Other Organizations, 1986-1989; 1991-1994; Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - New York Correspondence, 1983-1986; 1989; Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - New York- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - New York- Long Island Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1984; 1986; Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - New York Miscellaneous, 1983-1995; Undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - New York- New York Lawyers Against the Death Penalty, 1991; 1993 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - New York- New York State Coalition for Criminal Justice, 1983; 1986-1987; 1991 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - New York- New York State Defenders Association, 1984; 1986-1987; 1989; 1995; Undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - New York- Old New York, 1977; 1981-1982; Undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - New York- Other Organizations, 1983; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - New York- People Against the Death Penalty, 1983-1987; 1989-1991; Undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - North Carolina Correspondence, 1983-1984; 1990; Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - North Carolina- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - North Carolina Miscellaneous, 1984; Undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - North Carolina- Other Organizations, 1983-1984; 1989; Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - North Carolina- Prison and Jail Projects, 1983-1987; 1989-1990; 1992; Undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - North Dakota Correspondence, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - North Dakota Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Ohio- Background Information, 1991; Undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Ohio Correspondence, 1982; 1984-1987; 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Ohio- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Ohio Miscellaneous, 1983-1984; 1987-1988; 1990-1994; Undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Ohio- Ohio Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1982-1991; 1994; Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Ohio-Ohioans to Stop Executions, 1987-1994; Undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Ohio- Ohio's Other Lottery System, Undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Ohio- Other Organizations, 1979; 1984-1985; 1987; Undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Oklahoma- Citizens Against the Death Penalty, 1987-1988; 1990-1992; Undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Oklahoma- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Oklahoma Miscellaneous, 1987; 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Oklahoma- Organizations, Undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Oregon Correspondence, 1983-1985; Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Oregon- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Oregon Miscellaneous, 1977; 1984; 1987; 1989; Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Oregon- Oregon Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1984; 1987-1994; Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Oregon- Other Organizations, 1989; Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Pennsylvania Correspondence, 1981-1984; 1986; 1989-1990; 1993-1994; Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989; Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania Miscellaneous, 1983-1984; 1986; 1989; 1991-1993; Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania- Other Organizations, 1979-1985; 1989; 1993; Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania- Western PA Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1984-1987; 1989-1990; Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Puerto Rico Correspondence, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Rhode Island- Organizations, 1989; Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - South Carolina- Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1984-1989; Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - South Carolina Correspondence, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - South Carolina Miscellaneous, 1981; 1984; 1986; 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - South Dakota Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - South Dakota- Organizations, 1985; 1989; 1991 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Tennessee Correspondence, 1983-1987; Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Tennessee- Death Penalty Resistance Project, 1983-1993; Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Tennessee- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Tennessee Miscellaneous, 1984; 1986; 1990-1991; 1993; Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Tennessee- Other Organizations, 1983; 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Tennessee- Tennessee Association of Criminal Defense Lawyers, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Tennessee- Tennessee Association of Criminal Defense Lawyers, 1990; 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Texas- Campaign, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Texas Correspondence, 1983-1984; 1986; 1991; Undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Texas- Crisis Response, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Texas- Dallas Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1985-1988; Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Texas- Endeavor, 1989-1990; 1993; Undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Texas- Justice and Mercy Project, 1987; Undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Texas- Lamp of Hope Project, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Texas- Legislation, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Texas- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Texas- March, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Texas Miscellaneous, 1983-1994; Undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Texas- Other Organizations, 1983-1984; 1986-1993; Undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Texas- Task, 1990-1993; Undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Utah- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Utah Miscellaneous, 1977; 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Utah- Organizations, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Vermont- Coalition Against Death Penalty, 1988; Undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Vermont- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Vermont Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Vermont- Organizations, Undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Virginia- Amnesty International, 1983-1988; Undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Virginia- Association Against the Death Penalty, 1985-1986; 1988-1989; 1994; Undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Virginia Correspondence, 1983-1987; 1990; Undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Virginia- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1990; Undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Virginia Miscellaneous, 1985; 1987-1993 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Virginia- Other Organizations, 1986; 1989; 1992-1993; Undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Virginia- Penny Resistance, 1984-1988; 1992; Undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Virginia- People Abolishing the Death Penalty, 1987-1989; Undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Washington- Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1983-1994; Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Washington Correspondence, 1983; 1985-1986; 1988; Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Washington- Legislation, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Washington- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989; Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Washington Miscellaneous, 1985; 1987; 1989; 1933; Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Washington- Other Organizations, 1987-1989; Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - West Virginia- Lighting the Torch Of Conscience, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - West Virginia- Regions, 1986; 1988; Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - West Virginia- West Virginians Against the Death Penalty, 1981-1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Wisconsin Correspondence, 1983; 1986; 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Wisconsin- Lighting the Torch Of Conscience, 1989; Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Wisconsin Miscellaneous, 1993; Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Wisconsin- Other Organizations, 1989; 1991-1992; Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Wyoming- Abolition Work, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Wyoming Correspondence, 1987; Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Wyoming Miscellaneous, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Journey of Hope, 1981-1997; 3; 2.85 cubic ft.
  This series features files from the "Journey of Hope" traveling marches and rallies during the early to mid-1990s. The files include administrative notes, programing notes, and some video, as well as fliers and correspondence from each event.
  - Address Lists, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Friends Service Committee- Great Lakes (Co-Sponsor), 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Articles- Indiana, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Articles- Outside Indiana, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board of Church and Society- United Methodist Church (Co-Sponsor), 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bulletin Inserts, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Campus Organizing, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Catholics Against Capital Punishment (Co-Sponsor), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Celebrities and Speakers, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Church Action for Safe and Just Communities- Christian Church, Disciples of Christ (Co-Sponsor), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Church of the Brethren, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Co-Sponsorship Confirmed, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Co-Sponsorship Form- General, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Co-Sponsorship Pending, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Commission on Social Action of Reform Judaism Union of American Hebrew Congregations (Co-Sponsor), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Common Ground Victims Families, 1981; 1989-1990; 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Contracts- General, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence- Speakers, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - C.U.R.E (Co-Sponsor), 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Daily Schedules, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Daily Schedules, Notes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Drivers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Must consult with an archivist efore viewing this material.
  - Education for Conflict Resolutions Inc.- Pictures, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Eighth Data Center for Justice (Co-Sponsor), Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Equipment- Electronic, Sound, Etc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Evaluations, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Evaluations, 1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Event Flyers, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Event Information- Before June 6, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Event Information- June 6, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Event Information- June 7, Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Event Information- June 8, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Event Information- June 9, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Event Information- June 10, Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Even Information- June 11, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Event Information- June 12, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Event Information- June 13, Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Event Information- June 14, Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Event Information- June 15, Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Event Information- June 16, Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Even Information- June 17, Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Event Information- June 18, Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Even Information- June 19, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Event Information- June 20 and After, Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Events- Page, Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Events Listing, Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - F.O.R. (Co-Sponsor), Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Flyers- Local, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Follow- Up Mailing, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Food, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - General Information Folder, 1989; 1991-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Goshen, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - In-Kind Contributions, Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Indiana '93- Budget, 1991-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Indiana '93- Common Ground Police, 1992; Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Indiana '93- Descriptive, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Indiana '93- Insurance, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Indiana '93- International Work, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Indiana '93- Items for Steering Committee, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Indiana '93- Media, Undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Indiana '93- MVFR, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Indiana ' 93- NCADP Support, 1992; Undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Indiana '93- Publicity, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Indiana '93- Religious Communications, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Indiana '93- Steering Committee Agenda, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Indiana '93- Survivor Contacts, 1989-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Indiana '93- Transportation, 1989; 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Indiana Council of Churched (Co-Sponsor), 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Indiana Maps and Info, Undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Indiana Press Release Material, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Indiana South Bend Tribune - Newspaper Clipping, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Indianapolis Peace & Justice Center (Co-Sponsor), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Inspirational Notes, Etc., 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Interview Form, Undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Journey 1, Portage-Gary-Michigan City, 1993 June 4-5 (Video-tape 1)
  - Journey 2, Michigan City- Gary, 1993 June 5-7 (Video-tape 2)
  - Journey 3, Gary- ELKHART, 1993 June 5-7 (Video-tape 3)
  - Journey 4, Fort Wayne, 1993 June 11 (Video-tape 4)
  - Journey 5, Fort Wayne- Chicago, 1993 June 11 (Video-tape 5)
  - Journey 6, Chicago- Campground, 1993 June 12-13 (Video-tape 6)
  - Journey 7, Bloomington I.U., 1993 June 14 (Video-tape 7)
  - Journey 8, Bloomington- Richmond- Louisville, 1992 June 14-17 (Video-tape 8)
  - Journey 9, Louisville- Indianapolis- Forgiveness, 1993 June 17-18 (Video-tape 9)
  - Journey 10, Indianapolis- Martin Collage- Goodbyes, 1993 June 18 (Video-tape 10)
  - Journey 11, Indianapolis- Goodbye- Racey, 1993 June 18 (Video-tape 11)
  - Journey of Hope III- California, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Journey of Hope - Coming I, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Journey of Hope - Coming II, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Journey '94- Georgia, 1993-1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Journey of Hope- Master Copies, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Journey of Hope Materials, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Journey of Hope- Pamphlet, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Lessons from Other Events, 1987; 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Local Event Form, Undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Local Event Information Form, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Local Organizers Notes, 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Lodging- Mc Cormick's Creek, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Lodging- Tippecanoe River, 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Logo, 1991-1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mailing Response, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mailings, 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Mailings- To Journey of the Hope List, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Mailings to Steering Committee, 1991-1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Manchester College, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Media Coordination's, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Media- National, 1993; 1997; Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Mennonite Central Committee- Great Lakes (Co-Sponsor), 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Mennonite Central committee- Office of Crime and Justice (Co-Sponsor), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Monthly Plans, 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation, 1991; Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation- Financial, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Music Musicians, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - MVFR Tax Papers, 1992; Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - N.A.A.R.P.R. (Co-Sponsor), 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - National Black Police Association (Co-Sponsor), 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - National Council on Islamic Affairs (Co-Sponsor), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - National Interreligious Task Force On Criminal Justice (Co-Sponsor), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - National Legal Aid and Defender Association (Co-Sponsor), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Clippings- Before and After JOH Indiana, 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Offender Aid and Restoration (Co-Sponsor), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Orders- Filled, 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Pax Christi, USA, Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Pictures, Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Pictures- Gary, Mich City, Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Pictures- Negatives, Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Pictures- People and Park, Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Pictures- So Bend, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Pictures- Texans Against State Killing March, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Plan and Purpose, 1992; Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Press, 1983; 1986; 1988-1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Press- JOH, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Publicity, 1992-1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Publicity- Marie Deans, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Publicity- Murder Victims Families Model Reconciliation, 1991; 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Publicity- Pat Bane, 1983; 1985; 1989; 1992-1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Publicity- Pat Clark, 1990; 1992-1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Publicity- Sam Sheppard, 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Quotes, 1992; Undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Recruitment, 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Reflections and Reports, 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Registration Form, Undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Registration Forms, 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Religious Communication- Lutheran, Undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Resource Materials- Buttons, T- Shirts, Etc., 1992-1995; Undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Roles and Responsibilities on Tovar, Undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Scholarships, etc.., Undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Seamless Garment Network, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Sign- Up Sheets, Undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference (Co-Sponsor), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Speaker Lists, Undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Towns- Anderson, Muncie, Marion, Undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Towns- Bloomington, 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Towns- Bloomington, Maps, Undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Towns- Chicago, 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Towns- Dayton, 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Town- Dayton, Maps, Undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Towns- Evansville, 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Towns- Fort. Wayne, 1993-1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Towns- Fort. Wayne, Maps, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Towns- Gary, 1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Towns- Gary, Maps, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Towns- Goshen/ Elkhart, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Towns- Goshen/ Elkhart, Maps, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Towns- Huntington, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Towns- Indianapolis, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Towns- Indianapolis, Churches, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Towns- Indianapolis, General Info, 1992; Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Towns- Indianapolis, March and Rally, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Towns- Indianapolis Meeting Notes, Etc., Pre 2/93, 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Towns- Indianapolis, Transportations, 1992; Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Towns- La Fayette, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Towns- Louisville, 1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Towns- Louisville, Maps, 1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Towns- Michigan City, 1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Towns- Michigan City Maps, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Towns- Other Towns, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Towns- Richmond, 1991; 1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Towns- Richmond, Maps, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Towns- South Bend, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Towns- South Bend, Maps, 1991; Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Towns- Terre Haute, 1993; Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Towns- Terre Haute, Maps, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Vehicles, 1993; Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Victims Articles- Quest For MVFR Members, 1983-1993; Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Video- MVFR, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Voice and Journey of Hope, 1992; 1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Voice Pullout, 1992; Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Want More Information, 1991; Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1986-1992; 4; 1.0 cubic ft.
  This series features files from the "Lighting the Torch of Conscience" initiative. There are programming files, notes on attendees, notes from attendees, copies of various mailings, as well as additional administrative materials related to the program.
  - Advocacy Guidelines, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Amnesty International, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Atlanta Statement, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Basic Flyer, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bills- Unpaid, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bishops, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Campus Work, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)